NICOLE NAM FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I'm a web developer who brings 7+ years of experience in the culinary, hospitality, and the art industry to the table, as well as recent experience developing dynamic web applications focused on the user experience, As a team player, I believe in a positive learning environment and that celebrating small wins helps you to stay motivated through your journey. My top skills include **Creativity**,

Collaboration, Problem Solving, and Culinary Operations
Management.

CONTACT

(647)-404-9660

NICOLENAM.WORK@GMAIL.COM

WWW.NICOLENAM.COM

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH KOREAN

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- React
- PHP
- Responsive Design
- Git
- REST Api
- Bootstrap
- Adobe XD
- Fast learner
- · Critical thinker

EXPERIENCE

BANQUET COOK

RITZ CARLTON HOTEL | NOV 2016 TO DEC 2019

Developed, strong organizational, and time management skills in order to boost productivity under pressure. Worked effectively with all team members to promote a positive working environment. Created, and prepared new and enticing menu items for the VIP lounge guests. Managed allergies with care and professionalism for guests' safety and satisfaction.

BANQUET COOK

FOUR SEASONS HOTEL | SEPT 2015 TO NOV 2016

Practiced the ability to handle multiple preparations and tasks simultaneously while maintaining 5-star quality. Demonstrated strong working knowledge of basic cooking and effective preparation methods. Prepared over 400 individual meal proportions, daily, while managing and training student/kitchen personnel.

PROFESSIONAL ACTOR

NEWTON LANDRY MANAGEMENT | OCT 2013 - FEB 2015

Performed in Shakespearean plays all across Ontario. Effectively communicating the character to the audience using voice, and movement.

FLIGHT ATTENDANT

AIR CANADA | MAR 2014 TO DEC 2014

Facilitated the highest level of safety by inspecting safety equipment, announcing and demonstrating safety procedures, and verifying passengers' compliance with safety regulations throughout all stages of flight. Directed and assisted passengers throughout the flight.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROFESSIONAL

RED ACADEMY | JAN 2020 TO MAR 2020

CULINARY MANAGEMENT

GEORGE BROWN COLLEGE | JAN 2014 TO SEP 2015

THEATRE ACTING

DONGGUK UNIV. SEOUL KOREA | MAR 2005 TO JUN 2009